Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, it's really
where we should be going, go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride away.
We're all together as well.
So let's just stay with the sun.
While our dreams are never-ending.
Heartbeat, we will be one, go ahead.
My darkness will swallow the world.
Just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow
we will find suspense And then commence
to live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our minds will never give up There's a
fire in our dreams And you can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
Out of the way! Clear out!
I heard you.
You okay?
I can't believe you had the gall to cheer
for me back there—that
was so embarrassing!
And a lot of good it did; I ain't
changed one bit—it's pathetic!
You have changed Bellamy!
I've seen you wield
your Haki powers—they're
stronger than anything
I've ever dreamed of,
which really pisses me off!
My pride shattered, but I'll
return your compliments!
You've changed straw
hats!
changed Straw Hats
Still heads here.
He can't be
Fighting
It's freaking huge!
I expected an actual fish.
Looks like a fish to me.
Then you better get your
vision checked, buddy!
That's a sea monster!
A wild beast!
The man at the cafe said this bridge was
reinforced with iron to
protect against them.
So there's absolutely nothing
to worry about, right?
This bridge is a piece of crap!
Usopp should be able to handle it.
We're the warlord! You handle it!
There's a time and place for
me to fight, but it's not here.
Any?
Better get ready.
Special attack! Green!
Two from behind!
They're going to crush us!
Now, real floor!
Keegan's at the bottom!
Spike!
It's called bombgrass!
Good work. Now keep it up.
Are you kidding me?
Look how many of those
things we're up against!
It's a pack!
There's no way we can fight them all!
We've gotta make a run for it!
Hey, Nose, unlock Caesar's restraints.
He's gonna help keep
those fish off our backs.
You're crazy!
He's just gonna fly away
and leave us for dead!
Then I suggest he reconsider it.
Ah!
That's my heart!
I swear you will all die a
miserable death very soon!
No one abuses a brilliant
scientist like Caesar and lives!
Bastille!
That's a major power!
No wonder the guy is
worth $300 million! Yes!
Keep running!
But seriously, Law, whenever
you're ready, we can use your help!
When I use my powers, it saps
away my stamina bit by bit.
I need to conserve every bit
of energy for the trip back.
Understand?
If my strength is even the least
bit depleted, we're screwed.
This is Doflamingo we're going up against.
What an imbecile.
Does he really believe he
stands a chance against Joker?
Just perfect!
The bridge collapsed!
What are we supposed to do now?
Plus, the fog's so thick, who knows
how much further we have to go!
Fighting fish headed straight for us!
Then we're in real trouble!
We can't let it destroy
any more of the bridge!
What stopped it?
Looks like we bagged one.
Then hurry and reel it in.
Today's the big battle.
Time to power up for it
with Fighting Fish Stew.
Yeah!
Whose voices are those?
People who live on the island, I suppose.
What do you mean?
You said it was uninhabited, didn't you?
Hey!
Who's on the other side of the bridge?
Also, how do we cross it? Get over there!
Did you hear that?
It's a human!
We gotta scram! Let's go!
Fly us to the island.
Huh?
Law, you bastard!
I swear you're gonna pay for this one day!
Stop complaining.
I mean, look how great the view is.
We should have flown over like
this right from the start.
Hey, why didn't we, Caesar? Huh?
Cut the crap already!
Do you have any idea how much gas
energy it takes to float three people?
I thought hostages were
supposed to be treated humanely!
The drag marks from the
fish ended this spot.
And besides us, there's not
a single person in sight.
The waters are filling up with shipwrecks
from the fighting fish attacks.
Up ahead!
What's that?
so this must be green bit gotta say the
landscaping leaves a lot to be desired
hey joker i'm here come
and get me save your
breath you see that beach on the southeast
side of the island we're gonna leave you
there at three o 'clock this afternoon
do you guys see what i see there
looks like a navy battleship
and it's not just beached
it's actually stuck
in the island somehow
how is that even possible
the cuts on those plants
look fresh it appears
that the ship has only
arrived on the island
recently its body doesn't
look all that damaged
so they would have had
to survive those fighting
fish infested waters
i'm sure the marines who
are on it aren't far
away we should be careful
what do they know what
we're doing here this
changes everything damn it
cesar i knew i should have
gagged you quiet down shh shh quiet i'm a
wanted man remember and
now that my boss joker's
officially resigned
from the seven warlords
there's no authority that'll
protect me if you leave
me here in handcuffs
then those marines are
sure to find me and then
i said be quiet if joker
gave up his status that
put him back on their
wanted list right i think
you're hiding something
of course not what would
i do i don't control the
navy by the way after we
leave here i'm thinking
about heading over to
green bit we cannot do
the transaction here
rethink this well they're
my enemy too look i'm
with these guys come on
where do i stand to gain
from the Straw Hats getting
captured if we're all on
the same side why don't
you take off my handcuffs
we have 15 minutes
here's the plan you two go hide
somewhere and be prepared to
snipe stay on guard though that
may be in the forest as we speak.
If you find anything, let
me know as soon as you can.
Sounds simple enough.
Now hold on, Law!
I didn't sign up for a
military operation here!
Robin!
It's dangerous! Wait!
Don't get too far ahead of me!
Wow, Usopp, you're really
making me feel safe. So brave.
Oh, real helpful.
Whoa!
Oh, no!
Dissi, don't leave me!
What's the hurry, anyway?
If you're gonna stop,
say so. Show yourself!
Are you the Straw Hat? Stop! You're here!
We know you're on the island, so
just surrender now, right? Come out.
We've got you Straw Hats
There they are, but who
are they talking to?
Somehow they anticipated
we'd be on this island
Tell the truth are you
good guys or bad guys?
We're Marines we keep the public
safe, so we're definitely good guys
We can't give you these.
We have a job to do here.
Tell us who you are.
What happened?
I can't see.
I'd rather not see this.
What kind of food is this?
At least we still got our underwear.
Now, Mille Fleur.
Campo de Flores.
Ah!
I caught one. Huh? Caught one what?
It's a person. What?
What's in her bag?
A couple books, some clothes. Candy!
A transponder snail.
Double check for any weapons.
There must be something on her.
Search inside her clothes.
Point C all clear, Roger.
Point A all clear, Roger.
No hidden weapons at point B either.
Let's not be hasty!
Don't try to run.
No funny business.
I see.
They've pinned my body to the ground.
You'll only hurt yourself if you move.
I sewed you nice and snug with
my magical stitch-ditch power,
so you're not going anywhere!
That sounds rather handy. It is!
Once someone gets a taste of my trusty
needle, they can't move an inch!
You big people were up to
no good again, weren't you?
There's been a mistake.
I swear I'm not your enemy.
In fact, I don't even know who you are.
I'm Leo of the Tantata tribe, a warrior.
Leo, all right.
Then could you tell me where we are?
And where's Usopp?
Uh, I mean the other big person.
He's not here?
Is he all right?
Your tall friend with
the long nose, you mean?
We captured him, too, in accordance
with our kingdom's rules.
So this is a country where only
little people like you live?
Indeed.
This place is known as
the Tantata Kingdom.
It lies beneath the great forest which
we proudly made with our own hands.
The great forest?
Oh, you mean green pit.
So you grow those giant plants.
The ones that cover the whole island.
That's right.
There's no plant, great or
small, the Tantata can't grow.
Everyone watch out. Kabu?
She has a strange power.
She can sprout hands and arms
like flowers on the ground.
Flower hands?
We've never grown hand flowers before!
That sounds real creepy!
Yeah, it must be magic.
It's the strangest thing I've ever seen.
They're fast, too!
Snatched me up before I could run!
Alright, that's something.
They must have carried me here
after that gas made me pass out.
I could probably use my power to escape,
and it might cause them to
panic and do something stupid.
So, spit it out!
What are you up to?
You've come to destroy
our kingdom, haven't you?
Not at all.
I grabbed your friend, but I only
did so out of sheer curiosity.
It doesn't matter why you did it.
Big people are not allowed to
see the tantada for any reason,
as the law states—you
must be put to death.
But why?
Whatever grudge you hold,
I have no part of it,
and if you must keep your existence, a...
a I swear I won't tell a
soul we met! You're lying!
I refuse to listen to your excuses!
But I mean it!
Okay, then, I'll let you go.
What?
Wow, that sure is a relief, huh?
She's not evil after all!
She gets to live!
That's all it took?
You certainly are trusting.
You can get up now.
Here, take your sunglasses, too.
Why, thank you.
Hey, Leo.
Oh, hello, Chief. Stop!
You can't release her. Don't worry.
She said she'll keep everything a secret.
And why would you believe her?
She said she means it, so it's true. What?
Okay, then. Works for me.
Are they all like this?
It is rather convenient, though.
Pardon our stares.
It's not often we get to
see a big person close up.
See?
Who are you?
The name is Gancho.
I'm known as the Tanta Chief, which
is what we call our king around here.
Welcome.
You can stay as long as you like.
Hi!
Nice to meet you.
Would you like to try
some simmered pumpkin?
That's so kind of you, but I'm in a
bit of a hurry. Hey, you! Over here!
We just baked tree sap cookies.
You want to taste one?
We're having tea.
You're welcome to join us.
I'm sorry, but I really must go.
We've got some grilled mushrooms to share.
Excuse me, but do you know where my
transponder snail went? Right here.
I released it into the wild.
This is bad.
It's not long until three.
I have to contact Law quickly. The exit.
Where is it? Wait a sec!
You can't be leaving already!
And here I thought you were nice!
If you leave, then hand over
your weapon before you go.
That's the rule.
I don't have one.
Give us a weapon or we'll
take everything you've got!
I said I don't have one!
We're gonna bleed you dry.
Take it all!
No! Wait!
Stop!
Is there an emergency?
You can't be mean to her!
Her partner is a great hero!
What?
Huh? Hero?
Usopp?
But where did you hear this?
I don't get it!
The big person with the long nose
told me, and he said he meant it too!
He's a legendary hero
come to save us at last!
Finally! Finally!
The girl came just so
we needed him most! Yay!
Awesome!
I want to meet him!
Husab, what did you tell them?
Why did you turn left?
Put a sock in it, Tiny!
I can't concentrate!
Okay?
Mom, who's he talking to?
No one!
Don't look at him!
Come on, I'm in a hurry here.
Not as much as I am.
If I get there late?
It's all your fault!
Now take me to the flower field already.
I'm going to shut up.
Owie ow ow dang it!
I really messed up.
That human's gonna see me.
Run you dummy!
Come on hurry.
Oh, no!
I'm so stupid!
I'm stupid and dumb and stupid!
I knew I would screw this up somehow!
You must be one of
those fairy things, huh?
That are a toy.
I'm not a toy at all!
I'm Wicca and I'm from the Tonchata tribe!
Now please promise you won't
tell anyone you saw me!
What now?
I can't look.
I think I must have twisted
my ankle back there.
I'm so dumb!
Wow, you're strong.
Look what you're doing.
Please, sir.
I need you to take me to see my
commander as quickly as possible, okay?
I mean, this whole thing's kind of your
fault when you get right down to it.
You stole my sword.
What was I supposed to do?
Stole it? Of course not.
It's my people's job to protect
the greenery of this land.
The big people call us fairies and give us
gifts in return for the hard work we do.
I took the sword as a present!
Look, I gotta go!
I'm supposed to be scouting!
My orders are to report to my commander on
the whereabouts of the Don Quixote family!
Please, we're running out of time!
I saw them honest!
I know for a fact they're on their way
to attack the Straw Hat's ship right now,
so we gotta hurry! What?
Oh, dummy!
You just told this guy everything
you were supposed to say!
Hey, you're not pulling my leg, right?
I'm one of the Straw Hats!
I really need to know!
Ah, don't, don't, don't!
I'm so dumb!
You're wrecking the whole town!
Calm down.
Once more, this is important.
Is the Don Quixote family seriously
getting ready to attack the Sunny or not?
I can't tell you that, but
they're not not going to do it.
Oh, I did it again, huh?
I don't have a transponder, Snail, so
there's no way for me to warn him about it.
Those four, huh?
That's not a strong team
Alright, I'm off to the sunny
Wait!
Don't leave me here!
I need you to take me back to
the flower field If you do,
I promise I'll show you the way
back to the sea Forget about it!
I can find my own way back
You can?
Then why are you going your own way?
I knew it. You're lost.
You'll never get there.
So,
if those guys knew where to find us,
they must have been following our
movements for a while now, is that right?
Uh-huh.
But we've been keeping a
pretty close eye on them, too.
You mean you fairies have
a beef with Doflamingo?
That's right.
Just forget I told you
that, okay? Damn it.
It's not just a ship.
The whole crew's in danger.
This is bad.
Hey, how far is this flower field?
Go up those stairs, there!
I said go up the stairs!
Well, and I thought I was stupid. Shut up!
Come back, Mr. Monkey!
I got you!
Keep running.
You'll find out soon enough.
Be wary of the police.
You're a soldier, aren't you?
Soldier!
What's up, Rebecca?
I saw the list of
competitors in the Coliseum.
I asked you not to enter.
Why did you do it?
Because.
Because I'll win. You'll see.
I promise.
When I do, please come back.
I just want you to stay with me.
If you cry so easily,
how do you expect to win?
Come on, we need to hurry.
Uh, are you sure? She's fine.
Let's move.
Brother, I don't know what's going
on, but you shouldn't make a girl cry.
That's why we must hurry.
I know I'm just a toy,
but I must protect her.
These useless tin eyes of mine
can't even shed a tear for her.
The appointed time for Caesar's handover?
Exactly two minutes.
Mm-hmm. Galick.
You there, law? It's Sanji!
Where'd you run off to?
And please tell me you found the factory.
That's the least of our worries now.
You've got to get out of there now.
We're not going anywhere.
Handing Caesar over is part of the deal.
Yeah, if Doflamingo actually
resigned from the seven warlords.
As it stands,
you're going to be handing Caesar
over for absolutely nothing in return.
Let me spell it out.
We walked straight into a trap.
That doesn't make any sense.
What do you mean?
So the news about Doflamingo
was some kind of mistake.
I find that hard to believe, Saka.
The public being fooled is one thing,
but the Navy HQ was also
duped by a false report?
I hate to admit it, but that is the case.
I'm headed for Marie Joie the five elders
and I need to speak at
once on this matter.
However, what's done is done.
You are to continue as
planned and keep onward to
Trafalgar law and Doe
Flamingo's rendezvous point.
Roger that, Sokka.
All units head to the
southeast shore, hurry up!
Idiots, there's no time left?
Thank you.